https://www.lifesafetyservices.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Close off canvas navigation Fire & Life Safety ServicesFire/Smoke Damper Inspection & MaintenanceFire/Smoke Door Inspection & MaintenanceFirestop Survey & Installation / Above CeilingArc Flash AssessmentLife Safety Drawings & ConsultingPhotoluminescent Egress Path Markers & Exit SignageInfection Control SolutionsUVC LightingUVC Air Purifying SystemHands Free Touchless Door SolutionsProduct CatalogLife Safety ReportingIndustries We ServeCommercialEducationGovernmentHealthcareHospitalityIndustrialLong-Term CareNew Construction ServicesNational Accounts ProgramArticles & VideosAbout LSSHelpful LinksLocationsGSA ContractGPO Vendor SupplierFinancing & Leasing OptionsContact UsView Our BrandsAbout LSS HoldingsSafenetixHughes EnvironmentalCareersClient Portal
0
888.675.4519HomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyStatement of Privacy PolicyLSS Life Safety Services® recognizes and respects your online privacy and is committed to providing adequate data protection and full compliance with applicable data privacy laws. This Life Safety Services Statement of Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) outlines our security structure and privacy procedures applicable to information obtained through LSS’s website pages. Privacy policies for information collected from any other source may be different than the policies expressed here. By visiting www.lifesafetyservices.com and its related web pages (the “Site”), you are accepting the practices in this Privacy Policy.How do we collect information?Information may be automatically received when you visit our Site regardless of any direct communication you may have initiated. Such information includes the name of the domain from which you access the Internet; the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; the date and time you access our Site; the geographic location from which you access our Site; and the Internet address (URL) of the web site from which you linked directly to our Site. We use this information to monitor and analyze the usage of our Site for marketing and other purposes. Also, the information we capture provides us with the ability to enhance our customers’ browsing experiences and to determine aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.We may also collect information which you provide to us through email or other entries you make on the Site. You may give us general identity information about yourself (e.g., your name, company name, business address, business telephone number, business email address) and more detailed information for specific purposes (e.g., special interests in products or industries, your job responsibilities, etc.). Such information may be used by us to assist in providing goods and services to you, as well as for our internal purposes and for marketing purposes. Information you provide to LSS via the Site may be distributed to sales, marketing or other appropriate LSS personnel, and a copy is kept on file in LSS’s main office.Do we use electronic mechanisms such as “cookies”?“Cookies” are small files placed on your hard drive that assist many companies in providing their services. “Cookies” deliver customized visitor experiences and are used to analyze website user metrics. At this time, LSS does not use data collection devices such as “cookies,” but could in the future.What about children?Children are not eligible to use this Site unsupervised and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use this Site in conjunction with, and under the supervision of, your parents or guardians.How do we safeguard personal information?We will strive to ensure that your personal information is adequately protected wherever it may be processed. Files are stored in a physically and electronically secured web server environment.Will we disclose the personal information that we collect?Data is collected and maintained by LSS’s website host, and accessed by appropriate parties at LSS, including, but not limited to, marketing and IT personnel. The data collected on this Site is for the explicit use of LSS and affiliated persons and companies. We will not sell or rent your information to any third party. However, we will disclose personal information when required or permitted by law or for purposes relevant to our corporate policies.LSS reserves the right to perform statistical analysis of its customers in the aggregate. This means the personal information you provide, along with other customers, may be evaluated by LSS in order to measure interest in, and to support ongoing improvements and enhancements to, LSS’s Site. LSS also reserves the right to perform statistical analysis of its customers individually. This means the personal information you provide alone may be evaluated by LSS in order to provide services tailored directly toward you.LSS reserves the right to transfer collected personal information upon sale of the business. LSS reserves the right to contact you via email, phone, fax, mail or other means to: inform you of new information and changes to the Site; to promote its goods and services; or otherwise as LSS sees fit.If you click on any links and banners which may appear on our Site that take you to third-party web sites (including, for example, sites which are not controlled by LSS), you will be subject to the third parties’ privacy policies. LSS cannot be responsible for the actions of any third-party web sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement of any other sites you visit.How may I access my personal information?You may contact us anytime to review the information which we collected about you and ask us to correct or delete it, if desired. Please see the contact information section below for more information.Where can I obtain further information about this privacy statement?If for any reason you have questions about this Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact LSS by mailing inquiries to:Corporate: 502-213-0431Toll free: 888-675-4519Fax: 502-964-1337Email: info@lifesafetyservices.comWhat happens if this privacy statement changes?We reserve the right to amend this data privacy statement at any time. If LSS updates or changes this privacy statement, the changes will be made on this page. It is your responsibility to check for changes. Your continued use of LSS’s Site and its applications following the posting of changes to this data Privacy Policy will mean you accept those changes and terms of this Privacy Policy.
Request A Quote
Request a QuoteHave a question about fire & life safety services? We are here for anything you may need. Need a quote? We’ll have it within 24 hours of your request.
Extended Site Map
Articles & Videos Contact LSS Life Safety Services® Careers Home Page About LSS Life Safety Services® Fire & Life Safety Services Industrial Cleaning Services Life Safety Reporting National Accounts Program Return PolicyContact UsCorporate Office908 S 8th Street, Suite 500Louisville, KY 40203PH 888.675.4519Fx 502.964.1337Em info@lifesafetyservices.comSocial
